{
    "id": "2b85db0d9c454925a5e41674c6362704",
    "title": "Idioms And Phrases Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "John, put a ........................................ in it! Can you not see that I am listening to the radio?",
            "description": "'Put a cork in it' means be quiet.",
            "answers": [
                "plug",
                "pin",
                "switch",
                "cork"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "6f0d7176e482478c914c6175bff8947e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She never missed even a single opportunity to put me ................................................ and that was the reason we decided to part ways.",
            "description": "To put someone down is to criticize him or her.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "away",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76e0af6476a64f068461b6d417a3c990"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you would not put your ................................................... in where it is not wanted.",
            "description": "To put one's nose in is to interfere in someone's business.",
            "answers": [
                "mouth",
                "nose",
                "arm",
                "toes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7a69cc4a1c84217af0d0c6168cf0cee"
        },
        {
            "question": "My neighbor likes to put .................................................. in front of me.",
            "description": "'To put on the dog' is to try to seem richer than you really are.",
            "answers": [
                "on the dog",
                "on the cat",
                "on the horse",
                "on the ass"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8fd57a53ceaf42aabf62da88e7a46268"
        },
        {
            "question": "They put him ..................................................... for fourteen years but that did not reform him.",
            "description": "To put someone away is to send him or her to prison.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "away",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d5636074f4c2418798963eef263b89ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not believe what she says. She is just putting you ..................................................!",
            "description": "To put somebody on is to fool or tease him or her.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa9aab2260c34d429ca4287434fdc4e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Feel free to call me if you cannot find a good hotel. I will put you ..................................................",
            "description": "To put somebody up is to provide accommodation.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "down",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6ca6781af144176ae16c59e65a2ebe9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I put ...................................................... on him but that did not help because he was already broke.",
            "description": "To put the bite on someone is to try to get money from him or her.",
            "answers": [
                "the plug",
                "the bite",
                "the nip",
                "the choice"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb39a57cf2e04d7c93f0b2d40484fa1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "During the identification parade, the girl put .................................................. on the man who killed her mother.",
            "description": "To put the finger on somebody is to identify him or her. ",
            "answers": [
                "the hand",
                "the thumb",
                "the finger",
                "the arm"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "81cd3998fe8e49d9b06b40b1aa6664f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "My girlfriend is putting ................................................... on me to buy her a diamond necklace.",
            "description": "To put the screws on somebody is to pressure them to do something.",
            "answers": [
                "the screws",
                "the lid",
                "the hammer",
                "the nails"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb07977c933a46d7b2c900f8dcea643d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He suspected that his business partner was putting ................................................. him, but he had nothing to prove it.",
            "description": "To put something over on somebody is to deceive him or her.",
            "answers": [
                "something over",
                "something on",
                "something over on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b84d8d84f634f0f82b3df0c515da5b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hostess really put ....................................................... to see that everyone was comfortable.",
            "description": "To put oneself out is to take pains to do something.",
            "answers": [
                "herself in",
                "herself across",
                "herself out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "01aca1a9ce69474d8b234b90cdc9cccf"
        }
    ]
}